I was walking in the dark I was looking for a sign I
heard a whisper, a distant sound Calling me to
higher ground I felt a hand reach out for me And
suddenly I could see The world was bright and new
Shine down on me. I can hear the call. It's
setting me free. It's a beautiful light for the
whole world to see. I can feel the promise inside
of me.
No more shadows, no more doubt I know what my
life's about I'm rising up, I'm strong and new
It's all because I'm following through I felt a
hand reach out for me And suddenly I could see The
world was bright and new I can feel the promise
shining down on me. I can hear the call. It's
setting me free. It's a beautiful light for the
whole world to see. I can feel the promise inside
of me.
Lift your hands up to the sky Let the feeling take
you high
Just let the feeling take you high
I can feel the promise
shining down on me. I can hear the call.
It's setting me free. It's a beautiful light for
the whole world to see. I can feel the promise.
inside of me. Feel the promise.
Hear the call. The promise inside of me.